react a javascript library for building user interfaces developed at facebook
react 一个用于构建用户界面的 javascript 库，在 facebook 开发
and released in 2013 it's safe to say react has been the most influential ui
并于 2013 年发布 可以肯定地说，react 是最近记忆中最具影响力的 ui
library of recent memory we use it to build components that represent logical
库，我们使用它来构建表示
reusable parts of the ui the beauty of react is that the simplicity of building
ui 的逻辑可重用部分的组件 react 的美妙之处在于 构建组件的简单性
a component has been brought down to its theoretical minimum it's just a
已降至理论上的最低限度 它只是一个
javascript function it's so easy a caveman could do it the return value
javascript 函数穴居人可以很容易地做到这
from this function is your html or ui which is written in a special syntax
一点 该函数的返回值是您的 html 或 ui，它是用称为 jsx 的特殊语法编写的，
called jsx allowing you to easily combine javascript with html markup if
允许您 如果您想将数据传递到组件中，您可以轻松地将 javascript 与 html 标记结合起来，
you want to pass data into a component you simply pass it a props argument
您只需向它传递一个 props 参数
which you can then reference inside the function body or in the ui using braces
，然后您可以在函数体内部或使用大括号在 ui 中引用该参数，
if the value changes react will react to update the ui if we want to give our
如果值更改，react 将响应更新 ui 想要给我们的
component its own internal state we can use the state hook the hook is just a
组件自己的内部状态，我们可以使用状态钩子钩子只是
function that returns a value as well as a function to change the value in this
一个返回值的函数以及一个函数到 cha 在这种
case count is our reactive state and setcount will change the state when used
情况下，值 count 是我们的响应状态，setcount 将在模板中使用时更改状态
in the template the count will always show the most recent value then we can
count 将始终显示最新值，然后我们可以
bind set count to a button click event so the user can change the state react
将 set count 绑定到按钮单击事件，以便用户可以更改状态响应
provides a variety of other built-in hooks to handle common use cases but the
提供了各种其他内置钩子来处理常见用例，但
main reason you might want to use react is not the library itself but the
您可能想要使用 react 的主要原因不是库本身，
massive ecosystem that surrounds it react itself doesn't care about routing
而是围绕它的庞大生态系统react 本身并不关心路由
state management animation or anything like that instead it lets those concerns
状态管理动画或类似的东西 相反，它让这些问题
evolve naturally within the open source community no matter what you're trying
在开源社区内自然发展，无论您
to do there's very likely a good supporting library to help you get it
尝试做什么，很可能有一个很好的支持库来帮助您完成它
done need a static site you have gatsby need server side rendering you have next
需要一个静态站点您有 gatsby需要服务器端渲染您有下一个
for animation you have spring for forums you have formic state management you've
动画 你有论坛的春天你有蚁群状态管理 你
got redux mobx flux recoil x state and more you have an endless supply of
有 redux mobx 通量反冲 x 状态等等 你有无穷无尽的
choices to get things done the way you like it as an added bonus once you have
选择来完成工作 你喜欢它的方式是一个额外的奖励，一旦你
reactdown you can easily jump into react native and start building mobile apps
做出反应，你可以轻松地跳入反应原生并开始构建移动应用程序
and it's no surprise that knowing this little ui library is one of the most
，知道这个小 ui 库是当今
in-demand skills for front-end developers today this has been react in
前端开发人员最需要的技能之一也就不足为奇了这已经在
100 seconds if you want to see more short videos like this make sure to like
100 秒内做出反应如果您想看更多这样的短视频，请确保喜欢
and subscribe and check out more advanced react content on fire ship i o
并订阅并查看fire ship i o 上更高级的反应内容
and if you're curious how i make these videos make sure to check out my new
，如果您好奇我是如何制作这些视频的，请务必查看 我
personal channel and video on that topic thanks for watching and i will see you
关于该主题的新个人频道和视频感谢收看，我会
in the next one
在下一个